How to attack when playing Aurora? The president split three gun lines. I am Xiaowu,
Give me a minute to teach you a formulaic approach to attacking the CEO. On the opposite side, cheat the first props.
Apply pressure directly forward. Click forward to add text to the left, immediately scroll to the right to synchronize the text, and knock out Lao Hei.
Immediately turn around and kill the Aurora, refresh and roll, and then kill the Birdman to complete the team destruction.
The Black Order Attack President can step on this to open up, and even if he is beaten back, he can save himself.
Don't be afraid of the Bone Throwing Lord on the opposite side. Roll backwards to isolate the gun line on the right and kill the Dragon.
Jin Bubu takes the information of the third person on the opposite side.
When I heard that I was going to kill the CEO at the door in one second, I jumped from the gun to wear down my health, and I immediately rolled to complete the breakthrough without any damage.
Collect information in advance. There is a small room. Use electric shock on the middle glass to try to capture the small room.
If you hear the feedback from the electric shock, you immediately roll over and jump behind the box. Falling off the bridge every second is equivalent to hitting someone who was not hit by the electric shock.
While fighting, lie down to avoid the gun line on the right. When you touch the head of a gun, immediately roll to the right to complete the destruction of the team.
Get the information at the corner, take aim and pull out the jump gun to open the breakthrough, immediately roll to the back of the box,
Looking at the CEO's door, he poked his head left and right and jumped with his gun to kill the Veyron.
The laser determines the position of the last person, the left probe, P.K. jumps to Rafe,
P.K. After the fragment gun rolls to the box on the left, fire the A.W.M. gun and kill it without any damage.
Breakthrough number thirty-six. On the opposite side, give the electromagnetic pressure position at the corner to compensate. It changed to continue pressing forward.
I tried to catch it, but failed and was touched by the opponent's lower frame, and the health volume was reduced. again,
The hedge roll collected two, and the last one was unable to save. Follow me, live broadcast every day, hate the bad guys,
Laser thinking, get out of class is over.